MARCELO AZEVEDO

marcellorhcp@gmail.com Rio de Janeiro - RJ - Brazil https://www.linkedin.com/in/marcelo-azevedohttps://github.com/marcellorhcp

PERSONAL STATEMENT

Working with infrastructure and technical support since 2014, with intense experience solving incidents using ITIL and Agile principles, which helped me a lot to develop my soft skill. Always concerned with the user experience. Impassioned by technology that loves to apply knowledge to solve problems.

Currently looking for an opportunity to work as a junior software developer using Go programming language.

WORK EXPERIENCE

IT Support and Infrastructure Analyst

At World Fuel Services
January 2017 - Present

IT Analyst in a global service desk model; managing a backlog of issues and requests, balancing project work alongside day-to-day support.

- I've been working with other IT teams geographically distributed, providing analysis, troubleshooting, maintenance and repair of computer systems and software for effective operation.
- I had the opportunity to be part of the challenge of bringing agile methodology to the company's
 infrastructure and support environment. Worked as an iteration leader for a year conducting the
 Scrum ceremonies and helping the other squad members to identify, track and resolve any blockers
 found on the Sprint or incidents queue
- I worked on the migration project from Mega ERP to Oracle R12 helping external consultants and users to have test, QA, development and production environments working properly.
- Employee of the Year 2019. Won the first place among all employees in the WFS Brazil branch.

IT Technical Support

At Harsco

December 2014 - December 2016

IT Technical support responsible for maintenance and asset control of computers, mobile devices and printers.

 Helped the company to take care of the incidents for Brazil headquarter and remote offices, improving team metrics and SLAs.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science

<u>Unicarioca (Centro Universitário Carioca)</u> June 2013- June 2020

Business Administration

CEFET-RJ

June 2007- June 2009

CERTIFICATIONS

AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner

Amazon Web Services (AWS)

Scrum Foundation Professional

CertiProof

COURSES

Learn How To Code: Go Programming Language

<u>Udemy - Todd McLeod | Ellen Korbes</u>

Fev - 2022 - Ago. 2022

Web Development using JavaScript

Cod3r

Fev. 2021- Dec. 2021

Discover (Git, GitHub, Linux)

Rocketseat

Fev - 2021 - Jul. 2021

SKILLS

Idioms

Portuguese - native | English - advanced | Spanish - basic